Problem Statement:
A pet daycare stores information about pets that belong to owners. An owner is
identified by an id, and their first name, last name, and address are also
stored. Pets are identified by their name and their owner. For each pet, record
their age and a description. Our pet daycare specializes in cats and dogs so
specific information is stored for each of these types of pets. For cats note if
they have claws and are social. For dogs we need to know their size and if they
are barkers. Our company supports animals besides cats and dogs. For other
types of animals, information about them and their type are stored in
the description of the pet. Our facility has several buildings that have an
identifying id and also a building name and year built. Each building contains
multiple rooms with a room number that is unique within a building. Rooms also
have a specific size. When a pet stays at the day care, the start date distinguishes
between particular stays for that pet. Additional information is the end
date and cost. The pet stays in one particular room for a given stay